https://www.step2.com/about/privacy/

Create An Account
Forgot Password?
Search
Cart
New Arrivals
Kids Toys
Art Desks & Easels Ball Activity ToysClimbers & SlidesCoastersPlay KitchensPlayhousesPretend PlayRide-Ons & Wagons Sand & Water PlaySportsSwing SetsShop Kids Toys
Kids Furniture
Kids BedsPicnic TablesPlaymatsTable & Chair SetsToy Boxes & StorageKids UmbrellasShop Kids Furniture
Home & Pet
MailboxesOutdoor FurnitureOutdoor SafetyPackage BoxesPet BedsShop Home & Pet
Gift Guide
Price: Under $30
Price: $30 - $50
Price: $50 - $100
Price: Over $100
Age: 0 - 2 years
Age: 2 - 3 years
Age: 3 - 5 years
Date: 3/15/2017
You'd be hard pressed to find a company that values your privacy more than The Step2 Company, LLC (collectively, "We", "Us", "Our" or "Step2") does.
When you visit our website you will be given the
opportunity to receive email from us. We know that some of the information you
choose to give us is personal, and we take that seriously. Read the statement
below if you'd like to know what we do with the information we obtain from you.
This privacy statement describes how The Step2 Company, LLC collects and uses the
personal information you provide on our Web site: www.step2.com. It also
describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal
information and how you can access and update this information.
Personal Information About You
When you send us personal information such as your email address, street
address, etc., we use this information for limited and specific purposes
including the following:
1. We combine
your information with data submitted by others. We use this aggregated data to
analyze purchase trends and identify common characteristics of our customers
such as what states they live in, etc.
2. We use
this combined information, along with any comments you provide, to
help develop new products and make adjustments to current products.
3. We also
may use information to help persuade retailers to carry our products.
We do not lend, rent or sell personally-identifiable information to our
retailers.
4.
In order to place an order you must first complete the registration form and
create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give
contact information (such as name and email address).
If
you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally
identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide
additional contact information (such phone number and shipping address) and
financial information (such as shipping address if different than your and credit
card number).
We
use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have
trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
5. If you
request that we follow up with you personally such as to help you find a Step2
retailer or to fix a problem with a product, then we, or someone working
specifically for us, will use this information to contact you as you requested.
6. If you
choose to receive email or promotional information via postal mail from Step2,
then occasionally (usually no more than twice a month), we will send you email
or mail about Step2 products and promotions. We won't clog your mailbox with a
bunch of spam, and we won't give your email address or postal address to anyone
else. That's just not our style.
How to be Removed from Our Mailing List
If you wish to be removed from our list, please click here to contact us. If you prefer,
you may call us toll-free at 1-866-429-5200 or by write to us at the address
below:
The Step2 Company
10010 Aurora-Hudson Road
Streetsboro, Ohio 44241
U.S.A.
You may
also follow the unsubscribe instructions located within all of the email
communications you receive. If you have registered for an account you may also
log into your account and manage your email subscriptions by choosing the
"profile and subscriptions" section and identifying which specific type of
communications you'd like to receive.
We
will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it
is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended
for maintenance, we might send you an email.
Generally,
you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in
nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate
your account.
Access to Personal Information
Upon request The Step2 Company, LLC will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If
your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire
our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change
on our member information page (if you have registered for an account on
www.step2.com) or by emailing our Customer Support at Step2-Company@Step2.net
or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information
listed above. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.
We
will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed
to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary
to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our
agreements.
Special
Notice for Parents: Personal Information About Your Children
We are extremely concerned about your children's privacy. We do not knowingly
collect any personal information directly from children, and we do not
knowingly place children on our mailing list.
When you
register we may ask for some general information about your children or
grandchildren. Specifically, we may ask for age and gender information. We
combine this information with data submitted by other customers.
We use
this combined information to help us better understand who is using
our products. Knowing this helps us develop new products and make adjustments
to current products. Again, this information is analyzed collectively and is
not personally identifiable.
We never
ask for your children's names or anything that could be used to contact them
personally. Under no circumstances is any information you provide used to
knowingly market directly to your children or to contact your children. If you have
reason to believe that a child's Personal Information was provided to us, please contact us,
and we will endeavor to delete that information and terminate the child's account from our databases.
Tracking Technologies
We The Step2 Company, LLC and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics
or technology service providers, use technologies such as
cookie and similiar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users' movements
around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive
reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.
We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), and for authentication.
Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our
website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.
Log Files
When
you visit our website we detect and may record how you got here and where you
came from. Specifically, we may collect the domain name or IP address of the
site from which you connected, the type of browser you used, and what search
terms you used if you found our site(s) via a search engine or link. We also use this information to measure the performance of our
site and to help us decide where to advertise our brand and products.
Local Storage/HTML5
We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we
partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity
also use Flash cookies and HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management
tools for removing HTML5.
Behavioral Advertising
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites.
Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website
and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
We will not give your email address to anyone else.
We DO NOT
disclose any personally identifiable information about you to
anyone not doing work specifically for Step2 such as a credit card processing
company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send
out emails on our behalf, and a customer service provider to manage our help
section. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal
information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. An
exception to this is when we believe in good faith that we are required to
disclose such information by a law enforcement agency or court of law, or in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, and when
we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply
with a judicial or bankruptcy proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.
In
the event Step2 goes through a business transition, such as a merger,
acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your
personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets
transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website
for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal
information.
Also, as
we explained above, we may combine information you provide with data from
others. We may use this combined information to help persuade retailers to
carry our products. The information we share with our retailers is collectiv.e
On a very
limited basis, we may allow carefully selected marketing partners to send
postal mailings to members who have signed up to be on our direct mail list.
These companies will never be given your email address and will not have access
to any information about you other than your postal mailing address. If you
wish to opt out of receiving these postal mailings you may do so by emailing us
at Step2-Company@Step2.net.
Security
The
security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally
accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to
us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission
over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.
Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
When
you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our
www.step2.com order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information
using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
If you have any
questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at Step2-Company@Step2.net.
Links to Other Websites
Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy
practices may differ from those of Step2. If you submit personal information to
any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements.
We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you
visit.
Reviews
All review content on www.step2.com is provided by BaazarVoice. All submission
and use of reviews and ratings is subject to BaazarVoice' policies, including
its Terms of Use, Usage Agreement, and Privacy Policy, available at https://www.bazaarvoice.com/legal/. Reviews posted at
www.Step2.com may also be syndicated.
If you wish to have your product review removed you may contact us at Step2-Company@Step2.net.
Public Forums
Our
website may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be
aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected,
and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal
information from our blog or community forum, contact us at Step2-Company@Step2.net.
In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which
case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Social Media Features and Widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets,
such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features
may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to
enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a
third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by
the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Single Sign-on
You can log in to our website using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider.
These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information
(such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like
Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your
profile page to share with others within your network.
Collection and Use of Third Party Personal Information
You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, shipping address and phone number.
This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided.
To request removal of such third party personal information from our database, contact us at Step2-Company@Step2.net.
Contest
We may use a third party service provider to conduct these contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personal information for any other purpose.
We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.
Your Acceptance
When you use our website, you acknowledge your acceptance of this privacy
policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our website. We
may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information
practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to
the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this
Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically
review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact Us
If
you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please
contact us at: Step2-Company@Step2.net or
10010 Aurora-Hudson Road, Streetsboro, OH 44241
×
Close
Cookies & Privacy Policy:
This website uses cookies. By continuing, you agree to our
Privacy Policy.
Accept
